truelearn.net 2016-12-08

# Privacy Policy - TrueLearn

Privacy Policy for TrueLearn, Inc. (TrueLearn) and COMBANK Medical DBA TrueLearn. Last Updated July 2014.   
**Information Collected**  
When you request additional information or register for services, TrueLearn will ask you to provide basic contact information.  
When you purchase services online, TrueLearn will ask you to provide billing information.  
TrueLearn uses common Internet technologies, such as cookies and Web beacons, to keep track of interactions with the Company’s Web sites and emails.   
**Use of Information**  
TrueLearn uses information collected to provide you with the services you request.  
TrueLearn may use information collected to provide you with additional information about the Company’s services, partners, promotions, and events.  
TrueLearn may use information collected to improve the Company’s Web sites and services.   
TrueLearn does not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes. TrueLearn may share information collected with other companies that work on TrueLearn’s behalf.  
If your TrueLearn subscription was purchased by a 3rd party as part of an “institutional subscription”, TrueLearn may share personally identifiable information with that 3rd party regarding your usage of TrueLearn’s services.   
**Payment Information**

Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.

******Communications Preferences**  
Every marketing email from TrueLearn contains instructions on how to opt out of receiving further marketing emails from the Company.   
**How to Contact Us**  
Questions regarding TrueLearn’s Privacy Policy or information practices should be directed to admin@truelearn.com.
